HEEJOON MOON

Integrated MS-Ph.D. student, Hanyang University, Seoul, South Korea

[LinkedIn] [Github] [Google Scholar] Email: wilko97@hanyang.ac.kr Mobile: (+82) 10-9183-6597

RESEARCH INTEREST

My main research interests include **Geometric Computer Vision**, **Visual Localization**, and **Spatial AI**. Recently, I'm focusing on privacy-preserving visual localization, but my research interest is not limited to this. I also have a lot of interest in applications of 3D vision tasks, *e.g.* robotics, autonomous driving, and 3D reconstruction.

EDUCATION

• [Hanyang University]

Seoul, South Korea

[Integrated MS-ph.D.] Department of Artificial Intelligence

Sep. 2023 -

- o GPA: 4.35 / 4.50
- Tuition fees are fully funded by Hanyang University AI Scholarship

• [KyungHee University]

Gyeongi-do, South Korea Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2023

[B.S.] Department of Software Convergence, College of Software Convergence

- o Summa Cum Laude (GPA: 4.03 / 4.30, Ranked #1 out of 80 students)
- o Tuition fees are fully funded by KyungHee University Software Scholarship
- o Majored in Robot & Vision Track
- Leave of absence due to compulsory military service (Summer 2019 Fall 2020)

Papers

International papers

- [1] <u>Heejoon Moon*</u>, Jeonggon Kim*, Sudipta N. Sinha, Je Hyeong Hong, "2D Feature Lattices for Privacy-Preserving Image Queries in Visual Localization", *Under review*
 - o Keywords: Minimal solvers (P3P, P2ORI solver) in visual localization, Non-parametric optimization
- [2] Heejoon Moon, Jongwoo Lee, Jeonggon Kim, Je Hyeong Hong, "Depth-Guided Privacy-Preserving Visual Localization Using 3D Sphere Clouds", in Proceedings of the British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2024
 Keywords: Depth-guided localization, 3D line geometry, Scene inversion
 [Paper]
- [3] Heejoon Moon, Chungwhan Lee, Je Hyeong Hong, "Efficient Privacy-Preserving Visual Localization Using 3D Ray Clouds," in *Proceedings of the IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2024
 Keywords: Minimal solver (5+1 solver), Generalized camera model, 3D line geometry, Non-parametric optimization [Paper] [Code]
- [4] Jiyoung Jung, <u>Heejoon Moon</u>, Geunhyeok Yu, Hyoseok Hwang, "Generative Perturbation Network for Universal Adversarial Attacks on Brain-Computer Interfaces," *IEEE Journal of Biomedical and Health Informatics*, 2023
 o Keywords: Universal adversarial perturbation, Generative models
 [Paper] [Code]

PATENT

• Privacy-Preserving Image-based Localization using 3D Ray Clouds

South Korea, PCT April. 2024

Je Hyeong Hong, **Heejoon Moon**, Chungwhan Lee

RESEARCH EXPERIENCES

• Spatial AI Lab, Hanyang University

Integrated MS-Ph.D. (Advisor: Prof. Je Hyeong Hong)

Seoul, South Korea Feb. 2023 - current

- Main research topics: visual localization, geometric vision, scene inversion
- Led to 1 CVPR, 1 BMVC, 1 PCT patent submission
- Recently Coworked with Dr Sudipta N. Sinha, leading to a top conference submission currently under review.

• AI & Robotics Lab, KyungHee University

Undergraduate Research Intern (Advisor: Prof. Hyoseok Hwang)

Gyeongi-do, South Korea Mar. 2021 - Dec. 2022

- Main research topics: Adversarial Attack, BCI
- Led to 1 international journal (Q1) submission

Projects

• 3D Reconstruction with Multi-View RGB-D Images

"Development of Moving Robot-based Immersive Video Acquisition and Processing System in Metaverse", IITP, Korea

- o Implementing 3D object Reconstruction pipeline from scratch using multi-view RGB-D images. [Paper] [Github](85stars)
- o Keywords: Multi-View, Feature based Registration, ICP Registration, Pose Graph Optimization

Turtlebot Manipulation with Optical Flow in Gazebo Simulation

Manipulation of Turtlebot in Gazebo simulation, directed by the direction of Optical Flow. [Github]

 \circ Keywords: Optical Flow, Teleoperation

• Image Style Transfer

Converting pictures of KyungHee University into several styles, based on AdaIN Style Transfer. [Project page Link]

o Keywords: Style-Transfer

• KITTI360 Visualization

Visualization of KITTI360 dataset, containing Lidar/Laser/Stereo point clouds and 360(fisheye) RGB Images. [Github]

o Keywords: Sensor-Fusion

Academic Experiences

• Invited poster session, Korean Conference on Computer Vision (KCCV) 2024 Busan, South Korea Efficient Privacy-Preserving Visual Localization Using 3D Ray Clouds, also presented in CVPR 2024

Aug. 2024

• Academic service as a conference reviewer

WACV 2024, CVPR 2024, ECCV 2024

• Programming Camp: Deep Learning for Computer Vision, KCVS

Virtual, Feb. 2022

• Summer School: Image Understanding & Signal Processing Summer School, IEIE Virtual, Jul. 2021

Teaching Experiences

• Student Tutor, Hanyang Univ.

Seoul, South Korea

Joining as a student tutor for a lecture.

Sep. 2023 - Dec. 2023

o Computer Vision: Making tutorial codes for LUKAS-KANADE optical-flow & Video anomaly detection

• Student Tutor, KyungHee Univ.

Gyeongi-do, South Korea

Joining as an undergraduate student tutor for lectures.

Mar. 2022 - Dec.2022

- o Robot Sensor Data Processing: Making SfM tutorial codes & documents for assignments, Q&A
- o Robot Programming: Making tutorial codes about SLAM(gMapping, ORB-SLAM, Graph-SLAM) on ROS Gazebo

SKILLS

- **Programming** C/C++, Python
- Frameworks PyTorch, Eigen3, Ceres-Solver, ROS, Open3D, OpenCV, Scikit-Learn
- Language English(fluent), Korean(native)

Awards and Honors

• LG Electronics Group Paper Award

June. 2023

Summer Annual Conference of IEIE 2023, [Paper]

• KyungHee University Academic Scholarship

Fall. 2018, Spring. 2019

for outstanding performance (Ranked-top 1 in each semester)

• KyungHee University Software Festival Awards

Nov. 2021

Campus Images with Neural Style Transfer, [Project page Link]

• Dean's List, KyungHee University

Fall 2018 - Fall 2023

Ranked top-3 or higher out of 80 students in the same year in each academic year